{"data":[{"MatchName":"match1","Match":[{"roundName":"round1","Questions":[{"Question":"Name any colors ","Answer":["RED","ORANGE","YELLOW","GREEN","BLUE","INDIGO","VIOLET","PURPLE","PINK","SILVER","GOLD","BROWN","GREY","GRAY","BLACK","WHITE","BIEGE"]},{"Question":"Name the days in the week","Answer":["MONDAY","TUESDAY","WEDNESDAY","THURSDAY","FRIDAY","SATURDAY","SUNDAY"]},{"Question":"Name the months ","Answer":["JANUARY","FEBUARY","MARCH","APRIL","MAY","JUNE","JULY","AUGUST","SEPTEMBER","OCTOBER","NOVEMBER","DECEMBER"]},{"Question":"Where people can swim? ","Answer":["SWIMMING POOL","POOL","POND","RIVER","BEACH","LAKE","OCEAN","WATER"]}]},{"roundName":"round2","Questions":[{"Question":"Name the solar planets","Answer":["MERCURY","VENUS","EARTH","MARS","CERES","JUPITER","SATURN","URANUS","NEPTUNE","PLUTO","CHARON ","2003 UB 313"]},{"Question":"Type the alphabets","Answer":["A","B","C","D","E","F","G","H","I","J","K","L","M","N","O","P","Q","R","S","T","U","V","W","X","Y","Z"]},{"Question":"Name prime numbers less than 100","Answer":["2","3","5","7","11","13","17","19","23","29","31","37","41","43","53","61","67","71","73","79","83","89","97"]},{"Question":"Name continents of the world","Answer":["EUROPE","ASIA","NORTH AMERICA","AFRICA","SOUTH AMERICA","ANTARTICA","OCEANIA"]}]},{"roundName":"round3","Questions":[{"Question":"Name rainbow colors","Answer":["RED","ORANGE","YELLOW","GREEN","BLUE","INDIGO","VIOLET"]},{"Question":"Name leap years from 2000 to 2020","Answer":["2000","2004","2008","2012","2016","2020"]},{"Question":"Multiplication Table of 2 under 20","Answer":["2","4","6","8","10","12","14","16"]},{"Question":"Name Popular Search Engines","Answer":["GOOGLE","BING","YAHOO","BAIDU","AOL","ASK.COM","EXCITE","ASK","DUCKDUCKGO","WOLFRAM ALPHA","YANDEX","LYCOS","YOUTUBE","AMAZON","FACEBOOK","YOUTUBE"]}]}]},{"MatchName":"match2","Match":[{"roundName":"round1","Questions":[{"Question":"Name common pet animals","Answer":["DOG","PUPPY","CAT","KITTEN","TURTLE","RABBIT","HAMSTER","MOUSE","PARROT","GOLDFISH","FISH","TROPICAL FISH"]},{"Question":"Name the seasons","Answer":["SPRING","SUMMER","MONSOON","AUTUMN","PREWINTER","WINTER","FALL"]},{"Question":"Multiplication table of 10 under 100","Answer":["10","20","30","40","50","60","70","80","90"]},{"Question":"Name the directions","Answer":["EAST","NORTH","SOUTH","WEST","NORTH WEST","NORTH EAST","SOUTH EAST","SOUTH WEST"]}]},{"roundName":"round2","Questions":[{"Question":"Name most popular superheroes","Answer":["BATMAN","SUPERMAN","SPIDERMAN","IRONMAN","WOLVERINE","CAPTAIN AMERICA","HULK","THOR","FLASH","GREEN LANTERN","WONDER WOMEN","AQUAMAN","SCARLET WITCH","JEAN GREY"]},{"Question":"Name the music scales","Answer":["DO","RE","MI","FA","SO","LA","TI"]},{"Question":"Name the popular fast food brands","Answer":["MACDONALDS","STARBUCKS","SUBWAY","TACOBELL","WENDYS","BURGER KING","DUNKIN DONUTS","DOMINOES","KFC","PIZZA HUT"]},{"Question":"Name different shapes","Answer":["ARROW","CROSS","CRECENT","HEART","STAR","CIRCLE","OVAL","SQUARE","CUBE","CYLINDER","RHOMBUS","PARALELOGRAM","SCALENE TRIANGLE","TRIANGLE","RIGHT TRIANGLE","PENTAGON","HEXAGON","HEPTAGON","OCTAGON","NANAGON","RECTANGLE"]}]},{"roundName":"round3","Questions":[{"Question":"Name popular smartphone brands","Answer":["SAMSUNG","APPLE","XIAOMI","OPPO","ONEPLUS","APPLE","MOTOROLA","MOBICEL","GOOGLE","NOKIA","MICROSOFT","LENOVO"]},{"Question":"Transport modes that you use to travel","Answer":["METRO","SUBWAY","TRAIN","RAIL","AIRPLANE","PLANE","FLIGHT","HELICOPTER","CYCLE","BICYCLE","MOTORBIKE","BIKE"]},{"Question":"Name the popular sports brand","Answer":["NIKE","ADDIDAS","ESPN","UNDER ARMOUR","PUMA","UFC","SKY SPORTS","REEBOK"]}]}]},{"MatchName":"match3","Match":[{"roundName":"round1","Questions":[{"Question":"Name popular softdrinks brand","Answer":["COCA COLA","COCACOLA","DIET COKE","REDBULL","PEPSI","NESCAFE","TROPICANA","FANTA","SPRITE","NESPRESSO","GATORADE","LIPTON","MINUTE MAID","MINUTEMAID","DR PEPPER","MOUNTAIN DEW","DIET PEPSI"]},{"Question":"Name types of music genres","Answer":["ROCK","R&B","R AND B","HIPHOP","POP","COUNTRY","LATIN","EDM","CHRISTIAN","GOSPEL","FALL","SEASONAL","JAZZ","CLASSICAL CHILDREN","DISCO","OPERA","FOLK","RAP","DUBSTEP","TRAP","INDIE ROCK","INDIE","HEAVY METAL","CLASSIC ROCK","PUNK","ELECTRONIC"]},{"Question":"Types of vehicles","Answer":["BICYCLE","BOAT","AMBULANCE","BUS","DOUBLE DECKER BUS","BULLET TRAIN","TRAIN","JET","CANOE ","CAR","PLANE","AIRPLANE","SCOOTER","AEROPLANE","MOTORBIKE","MOTOR RACING","HOT AIR BALLOON","CABLE CAR","HELICOPTER","BIKE"]},{"Question":"What alphabets come between B to P","Answer":["C","D","E","F","G","H","I","J","K","L","M","N","O"]}]},{"roundName":"round2","Questions":[{"Question":"Indoor games to play with kids","Answer":["ISPY","SPY","HIDE AND SEEK","SIMON SAYS","MUSICAL CHAIRS","CHARADES","SCRABBLE","CROSSWORD","PICTIONARY","UNO","MONOPLY","TAMBOLA","HOUSIE","CHESS","CARROM","TABLE TENNIS","LUDO","BILLIARDS","POOL","PLAYSTATION","WII","PLAYING CARDS","CARDS"]},{"Question":"Name any fruits with P","Answer":["PAPAYA","PASSION FRUIT","PAW PAW","PEACH","PEAR","PINEAPPLE","PLUM","PITAYA","PERSIMMON"]},{"Question":"Name gadgets that apple sell ","Answer":["MAC","IPHONE","IWATCH","IPAD","IPOD","HOMEPOD","IMAC","MACBOOK","MACBOOK AIR","MACBOOK PRO","HEADPHONE","TV","AIRPODS","AIRPODS MAX"]},{"Question":"Name type of payment cards","Answer":["DEBIT","CREDIT","REVOLVING","PREPAID","VIRTUAL","AQUA","DEBIT","CREDIT CARD"]}]},{"roundName":"round3","Questions":[{"Question":"Name type of payment cards","Answer":["VOLKSWAGEN","TOYOTA","RENAULT","NISSAN","MITSUBISHI ALLIANCE","GENERAL MOTORS","HYUNDAI","FORD","HONDA MOTOR","FIAT","SUZUKI","BMW","AUDI","MERCEDES","TESLA","MAZDA","SEAT","TATA","FERRARI","VOLVO","SUBARU","BYD","FAW","KIA","GAC"]},{"Question":"Transport modes that you use to travel","Answer":["METRO","SUBWAY","TRAIN","RAIL","AIRPLANE","PLANE","FLIGHT","HELICOPTER","CYCLE","BICYCLE","MOTORBIKE","BIKE"]},{"Question":"Name the popular male outfit","Answer":["SWEATER","GLOVES","JEANS","PANTS","SHIRT","CAP","SUIT","SINGLET","JACKET","SHORTS","VEST","JUMPER","BLAZER","UNDERWEAR","UNDERSHIRT","SWIMSUIT"]}]}]}]}